cornucopia3d.com 2007-12-25

# Cornucopia -

E-on software is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy summarizes the policies of e-on software regarding the collection, transfer, and use of personal information on this Site, and regarding security measures e-on software employs to protect such personal information. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of this Site.

Please be aware that this Site may contain links to third-party web sites that may or may not have similar privacy policies, that this Privacy Policy does not apply to such web sites, and that e-on software is not responsible for the privacy practices, content, or conduct of or on such web sites. By using this Site, our services, or purchasing our products you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.

## Collection of Information

This Site collects a variety of personal information. Personal information such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and other information may be collected from you in order to, among other things: (i) respond to a request for additional information about e-on software or e-on software products/services; (ii) provide you with assistance in the use of e-on software products/services; (iii) permit you to download information or data or products from this Site; (iv) customize and enhance your visits to this Site; (v) report a problem with this Site; (vi) enter a survey or contest or participate in a promotion. Our goal is to inform you of the personal information we are collecting and the purposes for which we wish to use such information. We will seek your clear consent to your personal information being used for the stated purposes and will only collect such information as is reasonably necessary to achieve those purposes. E-on software will clearly inform you as to information that it requires to proceed with said purpose and information that is merely optional. If you elect not to provide required information e-on software may not be able to comply with your request or provide certain services.

If you contact e-on software, we may keep a record of that correspondence. When you purchase or download products/services from the online store area of this Site, e-on software and/or e-on software's e-commerce service provider(s) will collect your personal information in order to process such order(s). Our online store is designed to protect your credit card information, name, address, email and any other information that you provide us with. E-on software servers are equipped with industry standard security measures such as SSL encryption. The personal information which e-on software holds will be held securely in accordance with e-on software's internal security policy and the law.

This Site logs IP addresses and browser information for purposes of system administration, identification of technical difficulties, evaluation of traffic patterns and Site usage, and otherwise providing content relevant to visitors of this Site. 

## Use, Disclosure, and Sharing of Personal Information 

**Under no circumstances will your personal information be sold or generally distributed.**

You hereby agree that e-on software may collect, maintain, store, use, transfer, and delete your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We provide your credit card information to credit card processing or authorization companies to charge you for your purchases and we provide your name and address to our fulfillment centers so they can ship products to you. Neither the fulfillment centers nor any credit card processing or authorization company is permitted to send your information to anyone else.

E-on software and/or its resellers, representatives, third party developers and/or sponsors periodically send out information regarding upcoming industry events, promotions, marketing activities, product releases and features. By submitting information to this Site, you expressly agree that your information may be transferred to these parties and that this information may be used for such purposes. When e-on software wishes to use personal information that has been collected for a new purpose not previously identified herein, the new purpose shall be identified prior to use. Unless the new purpose is required by law, your consent shall be obtained before the information is used for the new purpose.

E-on software will release personal information to other parties other than as provided herein only with your express consent, unless (i) releasing such information is otherwise required by applicable law, statute, regulation, ordinance, or court order or (ii) e-on software has reason to believe that disclosing such information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms and Conditions of Use or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) e-on software's rights or property, other e-on software users, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities or (iii) if through participation in a special offer you agreed to release personal information as a requirement for participating in the special offer or (iv) e-on software is required to do so in order to provide prompt service for support or logistical reasons. Where e-on software does release your personal information to e-on software clients or business partners other than as provided herein, e-on software will first require them to agree to use such personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and only for the purposes for which it was collected.

The disclosure of personal information as contemplated in this Privacy Policy may be to a party outside your home jurisdiction. In particular, if you are based in the European Union, information may be transferred to jurisdictions outside the European Union that may not have equivalent laws and rules to protect personal information. By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you also consent to the transfer of your personal information as described herein.

E-on software reserves the right to use aggregated data (data that is not individually identifiable). Such aggregate uses could include, but are not limited to, meeting e-on software's marketing and business objectives.

## Accessing, Modifying, or Removing Information 

Under applicable laws, statutes, regulations, or ordinances, you have the right to (i) check whether e-on software holds personal information collected about you through this Site, (ii) access such personal information, and (iii) correct any personal information about you that is inaccurate. If you would like e-on software to update or delete your information from e-on software's records, please contact e-on software's Online Support Services. You can directly modify or remove your registration information yourself using our Secure Online Registration service. E-on software will require reasonable proof of your identity before letting you access or modify your personal information.

## Security and Integrity 

When you provide personal information to this Site, such information is stored on secured servers that are protected by this Privacy Policy. E-on software takes reasonable steps to protect your personal information from loss, misuse, or other unauthorized uses, and to remove your personal information when it is no longer required for its intended purposes. E-on software cannot, however, guarantee that loss, misuse, or unauthorized use will never occur (e.g., that someone will not overcome our security measures), and makes no representations or warranties to this effect.

## Children

This Site is a general audience site which is neither designed nor intended to collect personal information from children who are under the age of 13. In order to ensure compliance with the provisions of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act children under the age of 13 should not provide any personal information to this site. We ask that parents supervise their children while online.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

E-on software reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time and in its sole discretion. If the Privacy Policy for this Site changes, the revised policy will be posted at the Privacy Policy link on this Site's home page. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will not have retrospective effect. Information collected by us will be dealt within accordance with the provisions of e-on software's Privacy Policy that were in effect at the time your personal information was collected.

## Business Transfers

The personal information that is collected by e-on software is considered to be an asset. In the event that e-on software, any affiliated company, division or portions of its assets are acquired by another company, such information may be one of the transferred assets. We will take reasonable steps to place a notification of such a transfer on this Site.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions, comments, complaints or concerns or require more information about this Privacy Policy, about how e-on software manages personal information or responds to complaints, or about how personal information is being used, please contact e-on software's Online Support Services.
